<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>黃鐘瓦缶 on Regina</title>
    <link>https://UJedi.github.io/categories/%E9%BB%83%E9%90%98%E7%93%A6%E7%BC%B6/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 黃鐘瓦缶 on Regina</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zn-Hans</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 15:24:15 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://UJedi.github.io/categories/%E9%BB%83%E9%90%98%E7%93%A6%E7%BC%B6/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Viva La Vida</title>
      <link>https://UJedi.github.io/moment/2019-05/m-viva-la-vida/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 15:24:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://UJedi.github.io/moment/2019-05/m-viva-la-vida/</guid>
      <description>I used to rule the world Seas would rise when I gave the word Now in the morning I sleep alone Sweep the street I used to own I used to roll the dice Feel the fear in my enemy&amp;rsquo;s eye Listen as the crowed would sing &amp;ldquo;Now the old king is dead! Long live the king!&amp;rdquo; One minute I held the key Next the walls were closed on me And I discovered that my castles stand Upon pillars of salt, pillars of sand I hear Jerusalum bells a-ringing Roman Cavalry choirs are singing Be my mirror my sword and shield My missionaries in a foreign field For some reason I can&amp;rsquo;t explain Once you go there was never, never an honest word That was when I ruled the world It was the wicked and wild wind Blew down the doors to let me in Shattered windows and the sound of drums People could not believe what I&amp;rsquo;d become Revolutionaries wait For my head on a silver plate Just a puppet on a lonely string Oh who would ever want to be king? I hear Jerusalum bells a-ringing Roman Cavalry choirs are singing Be my mirror my sword and shield</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>大侦探皮卡丘</title>
      <link>https://UJedi.github.io/moment/2019-05/mv-%E5%A4%A7%E4%BE%A6%E6%8E%A2%E7%9A%AE%E5%8D%A1%E4%B8%98/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 18:25:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://UJedi.github.io/moment/2019-05/mv-%E5%A4%A7%E4%BE%A6%E6%8E%A2%E7%9A%AE%E5%8D%A1%E4%B8%98/</guid>
      <description>References Version Control Version Action Time 1.0 Init 2019-05-09</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carole &amp; Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://UJedi.github.io/moment/2019-05/c-caroletuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 18:01:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://UJedi.github.io/moment/2019-05/c-caroletuesday/</guid>
      <description>References Version Control Version Action Time 1.0 Init 2019-05-09</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>